Everyone makes kites and tasty food on Teej.  Have
you ever sown gram in your name on Teej
?  After flying kites for a long time in the morning,
I told him, I have
flown enough kites.  Now come on, feed me something tasty too.  I was
just late in speaking.  He
brought pizza and sandwiches for us.  And
brother became very happy as soon as he saw the pizza.
Then we sat together and enjoyed pizza.
After this I got
ready by wearing a beautiful lehenga.  Here mother was also
ready with soaked gram.  Meanwhile
Tai ji also arrived.  First of all I
took everyone's blessings and then we set out to
sow gram in our respective names.  On the way
we also met a mother and I
took her blessings too.  Then we reached the place where gram was being sown,
here everyone
sowed gram in their name one by one and
after sowing the gram, they shook them and pressed them well into the soil.
By the way, how many of you
know about this ritual of Teej?
Please do let us know by commenting.  After this we
exchanged our grams with each other and
celebrated like this with laughter.  We
celebrated our festival of memories.